Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 544 records, 1930-2013 IBT0051
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Teamster Records, Series 4
  This series is divided into four subseries: Conference and Meeting Minutes and Agendas; By-Laws, Constitutions, and Rosters; Miscellaneous Publications, Correspondence, and Memos; Ledgers. Folders are arranged alphabetically by title. Folder titles for the third subseries were retained as much as possible. Ledgers are arranged by size and by date when possible.
  The materials of this series include conference/meeting minutes and agendas, union by-laws, constitutions, ritual booklets, rosters, pension and health plans, ledgers, and miscellaneous publications, correspondence, and memoranda. The bulk of the meeting minutes and agendas are from the Central States Joint Area Committee and National Automobile Transporters. The majority of the ledgers are from Local 387. These materials range in date from 1930-2006.
  - Conference and Meeting Minutes and Agendas, Series 4 Subseries 1
    - Central States Joint Area Committee, 1968; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/2], 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/2], 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/4], 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/4], 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [3/4], 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [4/4], 1970; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/9], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/9], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [3/9], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [4/9], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [5/9], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [6/9], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [7/9], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [8/9], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [9/9], 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/3], 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/3], 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [3/3], 1972; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/4], 1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/4], 1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [3/4], 1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [4/4], 1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/2], 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/2], 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/2], 1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/2], 1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/2], 1981; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/2], 1981; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/3], 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/3], 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [3/3], 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/3], 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/3], 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [3/3], 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/2], 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/2], 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/2], 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/2], 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [1/2], 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee [2/2], 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Central States Joint Area Committee, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Central-Southern Conference, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Central-Southern Conference, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Central-Southern Conference, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Central-Southern Conference, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Central-Southern Conference, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Central-Southern Conference, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Central-Southern Conference, 1987-1990; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Executive Board and General Membership, 1970-1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Executive Board and General Membership, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Executive Board and General Membership, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder data_value_missing_a70a9c25a27ed048533c593372cd0205)
    - Executive Board and General Membership, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Executive Board and General Membership, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Executive Board and General Membership, 1994-2011; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1969; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - National Automobile Transporters [1/2], 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - National Automobile Transporters [2/2], 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - National Automobile Transporters [1/2], 1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - National Automobile Transporters [2/2], 1978; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - National Automobile Transporters [1/2], 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - National Automobile Transporters [2/2], 1979; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - National Automobile Transporters [1/2], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - National Automobile Transporters [2/2], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - National Automobile Transporters [1/2], 1981; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - National Automobile Transporters [2/2], 1981; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - National Automobile Transporters, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Over the Road Cartage [1/2], 1976-1977; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Over the Road Cartage [2/2], 1976-1977; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - 13th Convention Officers' Report, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - 21st Convention Proceedings [1/3], 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - 21st Convention Proceedings [2/3], 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - 21st Convention Proceedings [3/3], 1976; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - 24th Convention Proceedings, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - 29th Convention Proceedings, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - By-Laws, Constitutions, and Rosters, Series 4 Subseries 2
    - By-Laws of Central Conference of Teamsters, 1971-1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - By-Laws of Teamsters Joint Council Number 32, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Constitutions, 1966-1986; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Constitution and By-Laws of IBT Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, 1957-1971; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Constitution and By-Laws Local 387, 1938; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Constitution and By-Laws Local 487, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Constitution and By-Laws Local 544, 1966-1977; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Ritual booklets, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Rosters [1/2], 1963-1965; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Rosters [2/2], 1972-1991; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Constitution, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Constitution, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Constitution, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, Correspondence, and Memos, Series 4 Subseries 3
    - 401(k) Plan Benefits, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - AFL-CIO Survey of 1986-1987 NLRB Elections, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - American Income Life Insurance, 1979-1986; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Area Report, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Award for Frank E. Fitzsimmons, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Bookkeeping System, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Cartage Employers Management Association, 1974-1990; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Central Conference Quarterly Volume 1 Number 1, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Central States Southeast and Southwest Areas Health and Welfare and Pension Funds [1/3], 1972-1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Central States Southeast and Southwest Areas Health and Welfare and Pension Funds [2/3], 1982-1985; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Central States Southeast and Southwest Areas Health and Welfare and Pension Funds [3/3], 1986-1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Compliance Audit Program, 1987-1988; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Congressional and Legislative Facts, 93rd Congress, 1973-1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Construction Locals Manual, 1986-1987; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Credit Union Statements and Newsletters, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Decertification of Local 221, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Downtown Council of Minneapolis, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Economic Stabilization Program, 1972-1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Election - Local 487 [1/2], 1976-1982; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Election - Local 487 [2/2], 1988-1990; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Election papers, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974, Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Executive Board File - Local 487, 1980-1990; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Executive Board File - Local 544, 1974-1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Fair Labor Standards, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Flyers, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - "Focus" Volume 1 Numbers 3-28, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Frederick D. Kraemer, Ltd., 1975-1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Group Insurance Plan booklets [1/2], 1963-1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Group Insurance Plan booklets [2/2], 1970-1983; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - "Harvard Survey Identifies Unsafe Truck Drivers", 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Health and Welfare Fund Financial Statements, 1984-1987; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - History Project, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Hoffa Election News, newspaper, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - "How to Win Strikes / A Union Strike Manual", 1991; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - "The John Morrell Workers' Struggle", 1987; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Joint Council Number 32 correspondence and memos [1/2], 1973-1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Joint Council Number 32 correspondence and memos [2/2], 1978-1986; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Joint Council Number 32 Jurisdiction Report [1/2], 1978-1990; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Joint Council Number 32 Jurisdiction Report [2/2], 1986-1990; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Junior Teamster Program, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Jurisdictional Dispute 120 v. 638, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Jurisdictional Dispute 160 v. 471, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Jurisdictional Dispute 289 v. 471, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Labor Amendments, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - "Labor and the Bible", 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Labor Institute, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - "Labor's International Hall of Fame 1999 Induction Dinner" booklet, Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Report, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Local 120 miscellaneous, 1997-1999; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - Local 544 Health and Welfare Plan, 1988; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - Local 544 miscellaneous [1/2], 1973-1990; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Local 544 miscellaneous [2/2], 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Merger Local 120 to Local 544, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Merger Local 909 to Local 487, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - "Middle Class Union Made" by Richard A. Levins, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Minneapolis Food Distributing Industry Health and Welfare and Pension Funds [1/2], 1973-1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Minneapolis Food Distributing Industry Health and Welfare and Pension Funds [2/2], 1974-1988; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Minnesota Transportation Regulation Board, 1983-1984; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Minnesota D.R.I.V.E. [1/3], 1974-1983; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Minnesota D.R.I.V.E. [2/3], 1984; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Minnesota D.R.I.V.E. [3/3], 1985-1988; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota D.R.I.V.E. Check-Off forms, 1988-1990; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota Workers' Compensation Manual, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Booklets, 1966-1984; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Motor Carrier Labor Advisory Council, 1975-1976; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - NMFA Employee Protection/Training Program, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - National Freight Industry Negotiating Committee correspondence and bulletins, 1969-1990; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - National Labor Relations Board losses, 1985; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - National Master Freight Agreement Layoff Report, 1983-1985; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - National Warehouse Conference Proceedings, 1948; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - National Warehouse Division Policy Committee Meetings [1/2], 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - National Warehouse Division Policy Committee Meetings [2/2], 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Owner Operator Information, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Pension Fund Reports, 1985-1987; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Racetrack Jurisdiction, 1984; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Retiree Benefit Plans, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Scholarship Fund application, 1986; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Stewardship booklets, 1968-1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Successorship Principles, undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Surety Bonding Local 487, 1974-1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Survey for Local 487, 1990; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Tank Truck Negotiating Committee, 1972-1986; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Teamster Affiliates Pension booklets, 1962-1984; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Teamsters et al. v. City of Bloomington, 1986-1987; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Teamsters Safety and Health Manual, Occupational Safety and Health Act of 1970, Bureau of Motor Carrier Safety Regulations [1/3], 1970-1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Teamsters Safety and Health Manual, Occupational Safety and Health Act of 1970, Bureau of Motor Carrier Safety Regulations [2/3], 1970-1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters Safety and Health Manual, Occupational Safety and Health Act of 1970, Bureau of Motor Carrier Safety Regulations [3/3], 1970-1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Teamsters Workshop, Session #24 [1/3], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Teamsters Workshop, Session #24 [2/3], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Teamsters Workshop, Session #24 [3/3], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Transfer and Warehouse Financial Statements, 1984-1985; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Transfer and Warehouse Pension Fund, 1981-1987; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - USA v. IBT [1/2], 1989; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - USA v. IBT [2/2], 1990; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Union Stewards, 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Wage and Dues Calculator, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Washington Update, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Warehouse Employers Pension Fund, 1972-1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - "What is the Teamsters Union", 1977; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - William J. Carothers, et al. v. Jackie Presser, et al., Appelants, 1987; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Women in the Workplace, 1984-1985; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Ledgers and Record Books, Series 4 Subseries 4
    - Federated Printers, Incorporated, 1970; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 141, Ledger data_value_missing_a3721512c24141d6e648d44686964ae7)
    - Federated Printers, Incorporated Deposit Book, 1961-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - General Meeting Record Book, 1962-1969; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - General Meeting Record Book, 1969-1974; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - General Meeting Record Book, 1974-1981; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - General Meeting Record Book, 1981-1988; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - General Meeting Record Book, 1988-1994; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Local 387 Cash Book, 1956-1975; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1951-1952; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 141, Ledger data_value_missing_f69b297f23b9f036ce3506e3d856d84f)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1952-1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 141, Ledger data_value_missing_5dd0766081cb6eb536c788c419baedfc)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1953-1954; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 141, Ledger data_value_missing_1c41691dc7de7d33b7cc27b5b9a189d6)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1954-1956; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 141, Ledger data_value_missing_a2ca52051f93e1649ec37249863f1e03)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1956-1957; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 142, Ledger data_value_missing_dfedefd72fb10c7d05d7ad1c9c93a10e)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1957-1958; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 142, Ledger data_value_missing_320c6e7daba901c4a15bdd47651f1096)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1958-1959; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 142, Ledger data_value_missing_fa2121b98a46477d97a2be7781eda30e)
    - Local 387 Cash Book, 1958-1960; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 142, Ledger data_value_missing_308e622ee4a6bc7a5e61e70c5315f982)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1959-1960; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 142, Ledger data_value_missing_5594b921120a842d773b2714546853a3)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1960-1961; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 143, Ledger data_value_missing_7184fea88366a8fc21770d6bfec6dfe6)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1961-1962; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 143, Ledger data_value_missing_f358dab9824051933d3d40b233043666)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1962-1964; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 143, Ledger data_value_missing_1976a660d1f5b8d93cf820c74c1432f2)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1964-1965; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 143, Ledger data_value_missing_3ac2f338fa58893718594c37cced1280)
    - Local 387 Day Book, 1965-1966; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 143, Ledger data_value_missing_aef60fbc466bd3bb5fd384513ace309d)
    - Local 387 Deposit Books, 1946-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1930; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 148, Ledger data_value_missing_0bb33b3e634081c6ff3705fcf4f1536f)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1931; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 148, Ledger data_value_missing_82fe7b4b21c7ab712b409f3c86a3e88a)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1932; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 148, Ledger data_value_missing_81cdb43580757cac0c7f6c31eed68d1a)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1933; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 148, Ledger data_value_missing_2244feae4906acc6e56fb96ae865c6a9)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1934; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 149, Ledger data_value_missing_7617a508290023f19118526f01fa4af2)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1935; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 149, Ledger data_value_missing_5eec4a8b92f85432e3f9063b459f9122)